# **Naomi Starr**

https://naomiportfolio.herokuapp.com/ I https://github.com/Naomi-github

naomi.starr.mail@gmail.com I 07592173755

# **Summary**

Junior software engineer looking to be part of a team that values inclusivity, feedback, continual growth and communication. 4 years experience as an administrator, skilled in prioritising and efficiently self-managing workload, reliable and consistently accurate data entry. Due to complete the Makers Academy bootcamp February 2023, where I have learnt to value test-driven development and agile team environments.

### **Technical Skills**

Languages: CSS, HTML, Node.js, Python, React, Ruby, SQL |

Testing: Jest, Rspec | Databases: MySql, Postgres | Version control: Git, Github

# **Experience**

- Test driven development
- Paired programming
- Agile team environment
- Engineered responsive, multi-platform, scalable websites that are SEO friendly using HTML5, CSS3 + BEM,
  JavaScript ES6+ and React.
- Debugging best practice using inspect element tool
- Backend API's connected through CRUD HTTP requests
- Responsive website development, CSS layout, promises and API requests

# **Projects**

## **Bowling Score Card**

• Developed using JavaScript(6+) through test driven development, using Jest.

#### E-portfolio

- Designed, developed and hosted an e-portfolio using semantic HTML5 and CSS3 (+BEM) best practises
- Included responsive and multi-platform support to enable the portfolio to be viewed on any platform and device

### **Library Website**

- Delivered My Library website using HTML5, CSS3 (+BEM) JavaScript and React best practises
- Improved website performance by compressing, caching and lazy loading images and components
- Included SEO, responsive, multi-platform and hosting support

# **Education**

- Makers Academy 2023 Software development bootcamp focused on object-oriented design, Agile methodologies, test-driven development and pair programming.
- Python Pro Digital Data Pathway, Learning People 2021 Python course covering a range of interrelated topics, including complex data types and hashing and encryption algorithms.
- 2:1 Environmental Science BSc (Hons), University of York 2012 2015

# **Work Experience**

**Aaduki Multimedia Insurance** *I Client Administrator* October 2020 - August 2022, Devon UK Delivered excellent service to 50+ clients a day, building brand loyalty, achieving an 85%+ monthly retention rate of clients, by providing support with product information and purchase processing.

**Exchange Bank of Canada** *I Processing Specialist (Contract)* March 2020, Toronto Canada Processed all incoming orders - verified and packed over USD\$1 million worth of incoming currencies per day and ensured daily balancing of books.

**Okta** *I* Administration Assistant (Contract) December 2019 - March 2020, Toronto Canada Meeting office management requirements whilst being a point of contact between internal departments and remote office management, negotiated contracts with vendors and first point of contact for all visitors.

**The Woodbridge Company** *I Office Assistant (Contract)* November 2019, Toronto Canada Co-ordinated with various departments to schedule office support whilst meeting all requirements of the brief and time constraints.

**Aaduki Multimedia Insurance** *I Administration Assistant* August 2018 – October 2019, Devon UK Led the social media team in creating content on various social media platforms.

**Mystery Shoppers** *I Quality Checker (Contract)* May 2018 – July 2018, Devon UK Quality checked primary data compilation and followed up with customers on all outlying data.

**Alexandra Workwear** *I Order Processor (Contract)* February 2018 – April 2018, Bristol UK Collected and compiled primary data, identified outlying and non compliant data through quality checks and data analysis.

Monteiths Brewery Bar / Waitress August 2017 - October 2017, Hanmer Springs New Zealand

Miles Better Pies / Cafe Assistant and Baker October 2016 - April 2017, Te Anau New Zealand

Take Two Marketing / Sales Assistant March 2016 - June 2016, Sydney Australia

Love Coffee / Barista July 2015 - October 2015, Bristol UK

York Conference Limited / Catering Assistant June 2013 - March 2015, York UK

Nolans Cleaning Company and Glens Cleaning Company / Supervisor April 2011 - May 2012, Bristol UK

### Interests

- Scuba Diving: Qualified Scuba Diver (BSAC Sports Diver) with over 25 dives across the globe
- Origami: Keen 3D modular origami maker, especially of plants and animals